Thank you for watching!
Loud and Loud
Nogizaka's favorite
Hello.
This is Bananama of Nogizaka Kenshi Hikari, and we're just getting started.
Thank you very much.
As expected of a carpenter, here he is!
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my
Se-nya-nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan-nyan
Nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan
Now, Mr. Himura, please announce today's project.
New Center Himura Training
We have a new center, Naki Inoue.
That's amazing, isn't it?
Now the new center!
The 33rd album hasn't started yet, has it?
Yes, we've been working on it little by little.
We don't have much time.
We have a lot of work to do for the summer single.
We're going to focus on the center in a short period of time.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's like a driver's license training camp.
It's like a driver's license camp.
Let's get it all at once
Let's take it all at once!
We'll dig deep into Inoue, who's working at the center for the first time in his new position.
and learn the skills necessary for the center at once.
New Center Hima Project
First of all, there are still many things you don't know about Inoue.
There are still many things you don't know about Inoue.
What is the prize money you can get according to the number of questions you clear?
If you answer all the questions correctly, the prize money will be 1 million yen!
This is impossible!
This price is relatively rare these days.
It's essentially zero.
It's just to get to know the members.It's all about knowing your members.
The maximum prize money of 1,000,000 yen is reduced for every wrong answer.
and zero yen for every seven wrong answers.
and the quiz will be terminated.
Inoue, you'll get your own questions, and you'll have to teach them in a weird way.
That's the worst!
That's no good!
Inoue doesn't know what he's talking about.
He might be a cheater.
There are other cameras... small ones, too.
They're all aimed at Inoue, so they're checking him out.
A little sacrifice.
Answer all the questions correctly, and you'll win one million yen.
Our first challenger is persimmon.
The persimmon-banana sandwich didn't quite cut it.
I'm sorry to look so unappealing.
It's okay, as long as you get the answer right here.
This is the important part.
You all have a chance to win a million yen.
If you miss here, you'll get a big disappointment.
Well then, here we go.
Question
What kind of name was originally planned for Nagi Inoue?
Four choices.
If it were a free answer, you wouldn't get it.
Here are the 4 choices.
No.1 Inoue Hiroshi
Number 2, Inoue. Right.
You're right.
Number 3, Inoue. Hana.
Cute.
No.4 Inoue, Haru.
No.3, Inoue.
Uncomfortable
I think it's possible.
I heard that if it was anything other than Haruka or Haruka, it would have been named like this or An Ayaka.I was just saying that if it had been anything other than Haruka or Haruka, I would have named her something like this, or Ayaka, or Ayaka, or Haruka, but it wasn't Nakicchan, even though she said she was torn between Aya Hayaka and Haruka.
It's "Nagi"... which is quite rare.
It's okay... that much is okay.
Come on...
A million yen. If you make a mistake, it's 500,000 yen.
No, no, no! What? What is it now?
I just called him "Nagi".
That's no good at all!
Please answer the question.
The second one is the upper part of the stomach.
Nagi is such a stylish name.
I thought it means "to hit" in Japanese.
Let's see if I've got it right.
Kimura-san, please.
What a shame!
Shame!
Shame! Shame!
This isn't it.
The prize money is half a million yen.
It's too early.
The correct answer is number 3, Inoue Hana.
You must be Hana-chan.
She was supposed to be Hana.
That's right.
I couldn't decide between flower or cleave or plum.
Plum blossoms were also available.
And Grandpa was like, "No, not Hana.
Grandpa stopped them.
Grandpa said a more cutting-edge name would be better.
So it became Nagi.
Grandpa knew that there was a reading for this kanji in the Manyoshu
"Nagi" in the Manyoshu, the oldest anthology of Japan.
Nagi.
It's a really good name, isn't it?
I want to say Nagi.I'd like to say "Nagi.
I'm really glad to be this old.
How long were you in the past?
I can usually get people to read as far as Inoue.
But I can't read it.
It was a pain to have to say "Nagi" once.
I see.
Kaki.
We still have 500,000,000 to go.
That's good, Kaki can give 500,000 to everyone.
One at a time?
One at a time.
How much are you spending on this?
If you answer correctly, you get to keep the 500,000 yen.
Then Umezawa tried his hand.
There was also a pattern with Inoue Ume, wasn't there?
That's right, there were two ume.
Actually, here's the question for you.
What did Inoue do recently?
I wonder...
No. 1, he wrote "Barefoot Summer" as "Naked Summer".
No.2, I said "Mikan" in Shiritori.
No.3, when I asked him to repair my refrigerator, he said it wasn't broken.
I grabbed a cactus.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Let's see.
That's funny.
There are so many different kinds, aren't there?
Actually... there's Inoue's answer, too.
There's also Inoue's answer, but it's a mistake made by a different member.
There will be more questions like that in the future.
If you think it's me, please don't give any hints.
Please don't give any hints.
So that's how it is.
That's why it's realistic.
This was not made by a broadcaster.So the broadcaster didn't make this up.
This is real.
It's real.
Well, wait a minute, but you have two choices.
Which one is it and which one is it?
Fourteen.
Why is it 23?
I don't think we're going to play this game.
I don't think so.
I don't know.
I have an image that you don't seem to do Shiritori.
I don't think they'd ask me to fix their refrigerator.
If it breaks, they'll just say it's broken and be done with it
I think I'd have to go over it.
I don't know...
I don't want to reduce this place
I don't want to cut back on this. If we keep going like this, we might end up with the shortest time.
Good luck!
Okay.
Okay, um...
I wrote "Naked Summer" for "Naked Summer.
Yeah. - Okay.
Uh, please.
Now then, is this the right answer?
Mr. Himura, please.
Correct.
You've answered correctly.
I'm so happy.
You got it right.
It's a very difficult question.
It's very difficult.
That's great.
What is this?
Ayuna Nakanishi and I were working on the showroom.Ayuna Nakanishi and I were doing a showroom together.
When we were asked what song we thought of when we thought of summer
I wrote it on the clipboard and forgot to add a foot.
I see.
But it was a big mess... having a naked summer.
That's not the kind of mistake people enjoy watching.
No, it really isn't.
Naked.
I'm amazed you got this one.
I'm amazed you got there.
I think you're more like that than you think.
And she's also a little loose and cute.
He's a little clumsy.
I'm so proud of you, Captain.
I'm glad.
That's great.
By the way...
This number 2 is called "Mikan".
Here, here, here.
This is... across the street.
It looks like they're across the street.
He seems like he's the guy from across the street.
I asked him to fix the fridge... and he said it wasn't broken.
It's a hot water heater.
That's terrible.
If you ask me, it's not broken.
I've never had a refrigerator break down before.
What's the problem?
It wouldn't close.
It would close and then open, so I called for repairs.
Five or six guys came to fix it.
What kind of repair work is that?
They came quite a bit.
You called me.
I was thinking, "Thank you very much.I was just thinking thank you.
I did a one-step bong and left.
And then he left.
And then I asked him later.
I found out later that the shelf was just a little forward.
So he pushed the door open.
That alone exposed five or six people.
It's not broken.
This one looks like a hot tub, too.
He grabbed the cactus by the feet.
This mistake...
This one's also a hot-dip.
What are you doing?
It's my first cactus.
I've never had a cactus before.
And a bi too.
I've never had a plant.
I've never had a plant before.
I can't speak properly anymore.
Keep a cactus.
I thought it was just for visuals.
I thought it wouldn't hurt.
I thought it would be soft and pretty.
I mean, it was tiny, so I thought...
It's quiet visually, right?
Just a little tap, tap, tap.
It didn't hurt.
I thought, "Okay, I can do that.
Ouch.
Come on out, come on out, come on out, come on out!
It came out fast!
Come on out.
We're in the same class, right?
Yes, we are.
This could be your lucky day because we could be talking about this.
I'm scared.I'm scared. I'm scared.
that seems to be the case
What were Inoue Nagi's hobbies when she was a little girl?
Hobby small
4 choices
Ah, four choices
Number 1, rock-paper-scissors-scissors
Ah
No.2 one person Shiritori
Shiritori is coming out
No.3 Hitori hide-and-seek
No.4, one-man game
Let's go to number three.
What is "Hitori-zumo"?
In this case, "Hitorin zumo" means "in front of God" or "alone in front of God" or "alone in front of God" or "alone in front of God.
There's a festival... where you're supposed to pray to God.
If you miss this part, you lose 250,000 yen.
I'll go on a hunch.
You're early.
What's your answer?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Mr. Kimura, is this the right answer?
He laughed.
Of course not.
The correct answer is... number 3, hide-and-seek.
I'm lost.
Inoue, what's this?
When I was little, I didn't like holding hands with my mother, and I didn't like being tied down.
I wanted to say I was free.
So I used to go to the local supermarket, and I'd play hide-and-seek with my mother, and see if she'd find me.
They'd say I was gone because I wasn't supposed to be playing hide-and-seek.
I'm playing hide-and-seek, and I keep thinking they're not going to find me, and I keep thinking they're not going to find me.
It's quite an incidental thing, isn't it?
I hide in all kinds of places.
But now...
Inoue, were you a bit of a tomboy when you were little?Inoue, were you a bit of a tomboy when you were little?
I am often told that I was an odd child.
Unusual child.
I've become much more of a noob.
I don't know him that well, but he has an air of strangeness about him.
Why are you looking at me?
What do you mean? I don't know. I just see it as a motive.
No, but, you know, a lot of the girls are a little crazy.
A lot of them are a little crazy.
They seem to have a strong sense of humor, though.
I'll stick to what I've decided.
But there is a scene, yes.
Strong-willed.
Yes, in a good way.
Yes, yes.
That's what I mean.
It's a little weird, like a present for Mr. Himura. A banana mini-sure.
There was one.
Isn't that a strong image to give that to me?
That was a real problem at home for a while.
Even his wife said, "What are you going to do with this?
I'm sorry.
Nagi Inoue's first experience recently was...
Number 1, picking up girls.
Number 2, going abroad alone
Number 3, the act of getting off the train once when it's packed
Number 4, that Takuan is a pickled daikon radish.
Hey.
Which one is it?
This one too, except for Inoue's answer, the other members' answers are all the same.
That's right.
He's appealing with his eyes... those big eyes.
Don't move your fingers now.
Which one?
I've come to two choices.I've come to two choices.
I'm up to two choices.
I've narrowed it down to the best pick-up and the third most crowded.
I've narrowed it down to two more choices.
Twenty-four is just not possible anymore.
I'm sorry, I didn't think you'd write a sentence for number four.
I thought you might know.
May I?
That'll be 100,000 yen.
I made a mistake.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Let me ask you a question.
Number three, when the train is full, get off once.
Please.
Are you sure, Mr. Himura?
You're smiling.
I made a mistake.
Wrong!
Amazing!
Zara!
Oh, my God.
Yay!
We're down to 100,000 yen!
From a million yen so fast to 100,000 yen already!
That was fast!
That was quick!
The correct answer is... number 4.
That's a lie.
He recently learned that takuan is pickled radish.
False.
He says it's not the best answer.
What's this?
I think it's takuan paste.
Huh?
You've had takuan before, right?
Yes, I have.Yes, we have it.
I don't think there are any kneaded fish paste.
Kneaded fish paste is steamed fish paste.
What's the shape?
Like a fish paste.
It's the kind that's cut in half.
Not all of them are fish paste.
Around here.
I've never seen pickled radishes hanging out to dry under the eaves of houses.
No, I haven't.
All right!
Yes, yes!
I don't think so.
What was that "ah" you said once?
I imagined something once.
There isn't any.
Takuan is radish.
I learned that takuan is pickled radish.
I just recently learned that daikon radish is pickled.
Really?
Takuan is that yellow stuff, right?
Yellow, pink, etc.
Pink ones too.
But aren't daikons white?
Yes, but I know all kinds of fish paste.
Odawara is famous for it.
That's what I thought.
You know that all of a sudden?
Odawara is famous.
That's true.
You know young corn?
I didn't know that.
I'm shocked.
I thought young corn was a vegetable like that.
But then I realized that young corn is corn that's shucked when it's still small.
I didn't know that!I didn't know.
Because you said young corn.
But you know what?
That's what it's called.
I knew that name because it sounds like it.
Young corn.
You can't eat all young corn
Young
In the previous video.
Yeah, but I didn't think it was a vegetable like that.
You knew that... you knew edamame was soybeans.
I don't know.
You said soybeans.
That's what I'm talking about.
Edamame is important.
I'm sorry.
By the way, the most difficult wave.
Who's this?
It's a persimmon.
What?
When I was taking a walk with Yuna Shibata that night, she kept on ringing her bicycle bell behind me.
Then the two older brothers came up behind us and said, "Where are you going, sisters?
They rang me up and picked me up with a bicycle bell for the first time
Shibata was there too? I wonder if those two guys on the bike ever come to talk to you in Tokyo.
No, I don't think so. It's totally possible in my hometown in the countryside, Chiba.
No one from Chiba, not even in Chiba.
So, one overseas. Who's this? Tsutsui.
Tsutsui, did you go abroad by yourself? Korea, but I had two days off in a row.
So the day before, I thought I'd go somewhere tomorrow, so I decided to go to Korea.
I thought I'd like to go somewhere tomorrow, so I decided to go to Korea the day before.
It's totally different... you know... it's amazing to go to Korea all by yourself... to get tickets, find a hotel, everything the day before.
I can't believe it. What did you do? Gambling?
If you're a casino player, you'd go alone.
One night in Hawaii. What were you doing there? What were you doing there? I went to the Nogizaka concert in my room.
Asuka's graduation live was streamed to me by Sasan.Asuka-chan's graduation live was streamed to me by Sasan, and it's on this tiny little phone.
Hisara-san told me Asuka-chan played the drums, so I couldn't go to the Hyomura event.
I knew that, but I was already drunk from drinking beer when I saw that... but I couldn't stop crying.
I know it wasn't about Hawaii at all, but...
This is Isoyo.
I'm still tall, so I'm the only one who's sick, and I've been riding around like this for a long time.
The next one is "Solo Journey" and "Will you keep the bounty?" Inoue Nagi is in the center.
The text from your father... is it from an e-mail or a line or something... the most recent?
Congratulations!
No. 2.
Right... No. 3...
No. 3.
Tell him to be safe.
Buber, which one?
What's your father's personality like? Quiet outside, but not too quiet.
He's quiet outside, but he's quiet at home. "Quiet" is a different word at home.
He talks a lot when he's sober, or when he's at home, but outside it's like a quiet bar.
I've already made up my mind.
I've already decided... why do you want a two-tag team?
I almost said "on top of what" but I think I told you that earlier...
You remember?
Do you remember?
4 days is the most irresistible time to talk about what you ate in Korea!
Samgyetang, samgyetang, samgyetang, samgyetang, samgyetang, samgyetang, samgyetang, samgyetang.
Let's focus on the quiz. Let's go eat some samgyetang.
Samgyetang alone? I'll eat alone. Hey, that's great. You're very brave.
Good luck, good luck, good luck.
Tsutsui, concentrate.
100,000 yen here may turn into 50,000 yen.
Decided? Yes. Then, please.
Good morning, Mr. Hiduro. Is my answer correct?
You're angry. What's with your expression?
What's with the expression on your face?
Zombie.
Correct answer is number 4, center.
Yeah, I think we talked about this.Yeah, no, I think we talked about this.
When? When you went to your parents when you left for the photo shoot.
I heard it, I heard it, I heard it, I heard it.
I told you at the time.
When did you do that? A long time ago.
A month ago.
Oh, that long ago.
I remember asking, but I don't remember the answer.
I didn't listen to you. That means you didn't listen to me.
Oh my God, what is this place?
I went home to call my family when I had free time.
But I only talked to my mother, not my father.
You were there?
He's not sober, so he can't talk at all.
Well, that's all right.
Well, in your mother's case, she talks.
The next day, around noon, my mom asked me if I wanted to go to the center, and I said yes, and then it was over.
What's up with that?
He didn't come home after that.
He told me your glasses were in the car.
He said, "Your glasses are in the car.
And after a while, he came back to the center.
What's going on, Dad?
The first edition of "Hitorisama Tengoku" will include a special bonus!
Tickets for the Tokyo performance are now on sale nationwide!
Second round of mobile selection for "Unter Live" has started!
This is Ayame Chachii, thank you for watching to the end!
Please subscribe to our channel!
First, Goo-janken-poi (rock-paper-scissors-scissors)
Bai bai bai!